Berat Ucar

Front-End Developer



- ✓ dev.beratucar@gmail.com
 - +905537457033
 - Ankara / Turkey

in Berat Ucar 🕝 Berat Ucar

• Berat Ucar

Education

Civil Engineering, Gazi University 09/2017 – 10/2022 Ankara, Turkey

Skills

HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SASS, React.js, Redux.js, Postman API, REST APIs, Webpack, Unit Testing, NPM, SDLC, Jira, Scrum, Agile Methods, CRM, Git, Github, Autocad, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint

Languages

English (B2)

Turkish (Native)

Profile

Junior Front-End Developer with 1+ year experience in the software development lifecycle (SDLC) in developing and designing user experiences of Internet/Intranet applications using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SASS, React.js, Redux.js MeetingW3C standards. Excellent analytical and logical programming skills with a good understanding at the conceptual level.

Professional Experience

Front-End Developer, Gaming Pro Market 03/2023 – 06/2023 | United States, Internship

- Worked as part of the team on projects; receive regular guidance.
- Worked closely with team members to create consistent, reusable, and maintainable code; designed new software systems or updates to existing systems.
- Coordinated and participated in implementation, testing, and support.
- Responsible for understanding how their work fits into the project objectives.
- Ensured each build functions correctly on mobile, tablet, and desktop devices.

Front-End Developer, Let's Rental Car

10/2022 - 03/2023 | United States, Internship

- Followed agile & scrum methods for the development of the product.
- Involving in building multiple UI components from design stage to production stage.
- Performed validation of completed sites including the debugging and testing of code.
- Designed a responsive website using Bootstrap grid system to layout contents that fit different devices including mobile, tablet and desktop.
- Cross-browser tested sites in Microsoft Edge, Safari, Firefox, Chrome and mobile browsers.

Projects

Single Page Application Project 🛮

https://github.com/beratucardy/spa-project You can visit my github for more projects and apps like this.